[crew] Ooh. [laughing]
-[alarm blaring]
-[door opens]
[footsteps approaching]
-[tapping buttons]
-[machine humming]
[Clem] Morrow.
Hey, Morrow, wake up.
Hey.
[machine stops]
What day is it?
Thursday, I think. Hey, listen, we got--
Is it a changeover?
-[Clem] What? No, listen, there's been--
-Why is the alarm on?
That's… Jesus, will you just listen?
There was a fire in containment. Not…
We got it out,
but there was a creature loose. Or two.
Well, not loose. Not, like, missing.
We know they… One is dead, I think.
Hey, it's the other way.
Two of the clam things got out.
You know,
the octopus with the long fingers.
And they got Captain Dinsdale and Bronski.
Captain's dead, but…
Well, you just gotta see.
I got them both in medbay.
Bronski… Zaveri said…
She used the word "compromised."
Hey, which…
She and Bronski are hooked up now.
You slept through that,
like, the last eight months maybe.
Hey, I recorded something,
if you wanna see?
Well, pretty vanilla stuff, but she
likes to be on top, which is sort of hot.
[Zaveri] We need to establish
some sort of protocol.
[Rahim] Listen, darling.
I've been drinking for so long--
-We're--
-A bit of… a bit of tobacco.
[Zaveri] That's not
what this is about, though.
I mean, come on. This is like you're…
-[Rahim] It's always my fault. Always.
-[Zaveri] Yeah, it is. In fact, it is.
[alarm dings, stops]
[Morrow] What happened?
Mr. Morrow, you're in your underwear.
-I said, "What happened?"
-[Rahim] Um…
Captain's dead.
I can see that.
-We, um…
-[Chibuzo] Oh, come on.
Thanks. I…
I tried to remove the creature, but
the grip on his throat was quite tight.
So, I made an incision… [whistles]
…at the base of the tail,
-and he just died.
-They bleed acid.
Clem said there was a fire.
Yes, in the containment room.
Sprinklers came on with the alarm.
Captain Dinsdale got there first,
put it out. Bronski was right behind him.
Two of the containment pods
must have been opened.
And the arthropod's eggs hatched.
-What caused the fire?
-I'm gonna be sick.
-[gags]
-[Morrow] Quiet.
I said, "What caused the fire?"
-[Rahim] Uh…
-We don't know.
[Morrow] But why were the egg crates open?
-[Zaveri] Morrow.
-No.
-I'm assessing the threat.
-[Zaveri] There'll be time for that.
Right now, the captain is dead
and my science officer is compromised.
How do we get it off,
if we can't cut it off?
[Chibuzo] I'll say it again.
The protocols are very clear.
"Any crew member who comes into contact
with alien life forms
are to be placed in cryo-sleep
for the remainder of the journey."
Which is two weeks,
three days, and six hours,
for those of you
not counting the fucking seconds.
So you're saying freeze him
with that thing humping his face
for the rest of the ride?
-What's the status of the other entities?
-Uh…
Chlamydia, you and Chibuzo, go to the zoo
and make sure
the rest of the creatures are secure.
I told you not to call me that, please.
I, um, I want to stay with Bronski.
M-Maybe I can find a way to neutralize
the acid or sedate the creatures--
No.
Morrow's right.
We have to make sure everything else
is locked down,
or our lives are about to get a lot worse.
Where's Teng?
Uh. Mess hall, I think.
[Zaveri] Tell him to help Dr. Rahim
put Mr. Bronski into his tube
and to prep the captain's body
for burial in space.
-[Rahim] Okay.
-Morrow.
Get dressed and meet me on the bridge.
-[clicks]
-[door opens]
[door closes]
Put them both in the air lock
and have done with them.
Is that engineering's official opinion?
What she didn't tell you was that
the fire fried our navigational systems,
and our engine relays.
[Morrow] Meaning?
Meaning, we were a spaceship,
and now we're a missile.
And we're heading towards Earth.
You should fix that.
Yeah, no shit.
-We're gonna be okay, though, right, boss?
-[sighs]
Boss?
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Let me sweep the place first.
And the lights are green.
If containment was broken, they'd be red.
[Clem] Right.
[sucks teeth, sighs]
-[chittering]
-[knocking]
-Incompetence or sabotage?
-[tapping buttons]
Are you asking me or are you telling me?
I'm saying
those are the likeliest scenarios.
Mother runs routine systems checks,
engineers do stress tests.
The random fire breaking out
in an empty containment room
in the exact panel
that controls both navigation and speed.
Bullshit.
[Zaveri] We don't know anything yet.
It could be equipment failure.
You need to call a ship-wide emergency,
so I can start an official inquiry.
Do you know the level of panic if I tell
everyone there is a saboteur on board?
I need to take this to Mother.
You were fucking Bronski.
-[chuckles] What do you--
-[Morrow] Company policy
forbids romantic relationship
between crew members.
How did you know that?
I'm the head of security for this ship.
I know everything.
[sighs]
We just…
You don't ever get lonely out here?
You're distracted.
-Your judgment is compromised.
-Wait a minute.
In the event
the security officer believes
that the acting captain
is not doing everything necessary
to protect this ship,
he may take command himself.
Fuck you. That's mutiny.
I am responsible for the well-being
and safety of my people.
And I am responsible for getting
this cargo back to Earth intact.
Those instructions from the company
are crystal clear.
Whether or not the crew survives.
Fine. Let's go see Mother together.
[chuckles]
You talk to the computer.
My orders are from Yutani herself.
Nothing matters but the cargo.
Not you, not me, not the fucking cat.
So, declare the emergency.
I'll be in security.
[Rahim chuckles] Another victory
for the enemy of reason.
What does that mean?
It means this space bug is proof
of how stupid smart people can be.
Smart enough to build ships
capable of space travel,
of splitting the atom
and decoding the genome,
but too stupid to realize
you don't bring parasites home with you.
Hmm.
He wasn't a good man.
But nobody deserves this.
[Clem] Why do they want
these things anyway?
-Weyland-Yutani?
-Yeah.
Ah, you little rascal.
It's power. It's always about power.
You've got five big corporations
that control everything, right?
But our guys want to be on top.
So, they send us out
to collect the most terrifying shit,
so they can use it to take over. Got it?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, got it?
-Oh.
-Be a nice guy. Thanks.
[speaks in Hebrew]
Come on, Teng. Leave that poor girl alone.
Or I'm gonna call the captain.
Captain's dead.
[chittering]
[electricity crackling]
[engines rumble]
-[tapping buttons]
-[machine humming]
[explosion]
[alarm blares]
[Mother] Fire.
Fire.
[crew member] Fire! Fire!
Containment breach.
Fire.
-What's going on?
-Don't know, man.
Containment breach.
-[groaning]
-Hey!
Containment breach.
[grunts]
[taps buttons]
[tapping]
Who are you?
[sniffling]
[sniffling continues]
[moans]
[both moaning, breathing heavily]
[both panting]
Almost home, baby.
[squelching]
I thought we were gonna be
collecting, like, rocks and stuff.
That's what it said on the paper.
A biological survey.
No.
No, geology
is the study of rocks and stuff.
Biology is the study of animals.
Oh, shit. Really?
You sure?
How do you know all of this?
Are you gonna eat that or what?
Yeah. I'm just,
you know, perambulating about it.
Do you know if you were to cut
that pie in half, and save half for later,
then each half will become a whole?
Now you've got two pies.
Wait, no, uh,
how's half a pie a whole pie?
Plus, the last time I did that,
you ate the other half.
I've tried that one already?
Uh, mate, if you want half of my pie,
you've just got to ask.
He's getting around the ship
-without using the halls.
-[Malachite] Who?
I need to see blueprints.
All the crawl spaces and access points.
Wait, what, are you saying
someone set the ship on fire?
Where are you on repairs?
The relays are severed.
Trunk calls need to be replaced.
We're talking days, not hours.
Whoever fucked us
knew exactly where the hole was.
Wait, boss, is he's saying that
somebody broke the ship on purpose?
You say nothing. Either of you.
Failure to comply with a direct order
from your security officer
in the course of a criminal investigation
will result
in a total forfeiture of shares.
Yeah. Just keep it quiet.
That's not a problem.
[Clem] Is it really? I mean…
you saw the footage.
It could be anyone, right?
The sabotage. Even me.
[metal rasps]
Is it you?
No, come on… Come on, I was just…
For example, I'm just saying.
[metal rasps]
Did you pull the communication logs?
I tried, but somebody
deleted all the files, so…
[device whistles, clicks]
…I'm running a recovery program
on them now.
[device whistles, clicks]
Think that'll tell us
who's behind all this?
-[device hums]
-Innocent people don't destroy evidence.
[buttons beeping]
Mother, this is
an official GR30 command change.
Dinsdale, RJ is deceased.
Executive Officer Zoya Zaveri
has taken command.
[tapping buttons]
-[tapping buttons]
-[beeping]
[scoffs] Fuck you.
-[tapping buttons]
-[beeping]
[cat meows]
[♪ "La Mer" playing]
[song continuing]
Sorry, Captain. My bad.
It should've been me.
Not yet.
Uh. No offense.
[song continuing]
[song continues, echoed]
There.
See that?
I'm going there.
When you miss me or you wanna talk,
just look straight up.
I'll always be there. Looking back at you.
So be good because I'll be watching.
[sighs]
[rumbling]
[Zaveri] Talk to me.
Do you want the public version
or the private one?
Mr. Teng, give us a minute.
Why?
So he can tell you
somebody blew a hole in the ship
after setting fire to our engine controls.
I am not an idiot.
Our saboteur knew just how to hurt us.
Our fuel reserves are down to 8%.
In 24 hours,
the ship turns from missile to arrow.
But I need navigation control.
The kid's welding a new column.
It's gonna take a bit of time.
[bangs on surface]
We need help.
We have to wake up the rest of the crew.
[Mother] Cryopod quarantine breach.
Cryopod quarantine breach.
I was in the toilet, ten minutes max.
[Zaveri] It was frozen solid this morning.
[Rahim] Bronski was frozen.
Maybe… Uh, I mean,
you'd have to ask Chibuzo.
But what if you can't freeze these things?
Their metabolism, we know they can
survive in a cold vacuum of space, right?
So maybe their metabolism
doesn't slow like ours.
-Call Chibuzo. I need her to--
-[Morrow] Stop.
It doesn't matter how it happened.
A specimen implanted an embryo.
The embryo hatched,
and now it's loose on the ship.
So we'll wake everybody up,
form search parties.
[Morrow] No.
Ten more people having feelings,
a saboteur on board, creatures loose.
-We don't need the headache.
-So what? We find some nets?
How big can it get?
Wait.
How big do these things get?
You saw the containment room.
If we shoot this thing and it bleeds,
the acid's gonna eat
through the hull of the ship
and we all die.
Electric, nonlethal.
You see it, you pull the trigger
till it hits the floor.
Capture, don't kill.
Clear?
[Chibuzo] Okay. Species 19. Log 82-32.
If the subjects
live off oxygen from blood,
they won't feed on dead animals,
no matter how hungry they get.
Take a picture. It'll last longer.
Subjects have been deprived of food
for two weeks.
What keeps you going?
Interesting.
Species19 will feed on dead tissue
if hungry enough.
That's enough out of you.
[gasps]
-[Rahim] Fuck's sake.
-Oh!
Where the fuck…
I-I don't know.
How did you get out?
Careful.
[Rahim] Shi… Fucking bastard.
Went for a stroll.
[Rahim whistles]
You must have left the top open.
No, I… I always--
[Rahim] Always. Yeah.
Zaveri wants everybody
in the mess hall.
Did something happen?
[Rahim] Bronski… [whistles]
…is dead.
Chop-chop.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Oh, God.
You haven't tasted the fucking honey.
You don't know what bitter is?
-Do you know what I mean?
-Yeah.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey, Rahim.
-How are you doing mate?
-I'm good.
-[kisses] You're my favorite.
-Thank you.
I've asked you guys about this.
Teng, you and Rahim and these cigarettes.
-I said, it's not my cigarette.
-Please. I've asked.
-I've asked.
-[Rahim] It's not my fucking cigarette.
-[Teng] Apology.
-[Chibuzo] It's not your place.
-These cigarettes.
-[Rahim] It's not my fault.
[Chibuzo] This is why I eat in the lab.
Just saying.
-All right, settle down.
-Come on, hurry up.
[Zaveri] Now look,
there's no easy way to say this.
Bronski…
We thought the cryopod
would contain the creature,
but it escaped, so he's dead.
-[Chibuzo] Watch it.
-Pardon me, Your Majesty. It happens.
Quiet.
-It's a xenomorph.
-What's a xenomorph?
Still in early stage development,
-but growing fast.
-Dangerous.
Our plan is to sweep the ship and
to recapture it, which is…
-[all chattering]
-Quiet!
-[Rahim] You're a muppet.
-That's company protocol.
-Tell 'em about the fuel.
-[Malachite] Oh, yeah, this is good.
[Zaveri] Thank you, Mr. Teng.
We've had a major fuel breach.
-The tanks blew. We're flying on…
-Fumes.
-Yeah. Yeah, we're flying on fumes.
-What does that mean?
-[Zaveri] That's enough.
-[Chibuzo] You're being so casual about…
[Zaveri] It gets worse.
We have a saboteur on board.
-What's a saboteur? Is that a Frenchman?
-Shut up.
-I'm declaring a ship-wide emergency.
-[Rahim] Bad Frenchman.
All nonduty-related movement is suspended.
-[Rahim] Suspended? That's fucked up.
-She said doody.
[Chibuzo] Okay.
Mr. Malachite.
Wh… Me?
[Zaveri] This is a meeting, not a meal.
Oh. [chuckles] Well,
when life gives you food, eat.
That's what my mum used to say.
-Shut up!
-[Rahim] Bless your mum, mate.
Don't fucking listen. Know what I mean?
-[Malachite] I'm just--
-Sort out your life.
Well, you're saying that
we can't leave our quarters or whatever,
so who knows
when we're next gonna be able to--
One sixteenth share, I'm docking you.
That's official.
-[Rahim] Ooh.
-[Chibuzo] Shit.
-[Shmuel] Stop picking on the kid.
-I didn't… Fuck.
-[Chibuzo] That'll be it.
-[Malachite clears throat]
The fuck is wrong with him?
-[Malachite coughing]
-[Shmuel] You're upsetting him now.
That's cruel.
[Malachite continues coughing]
[Chibuzo] Hey, hey, hey.
That time of the month, darling?
[Malachite] Fuck me, that was hot.
Two people are dead.
We've lost creature containment.
And one of you…
Look around.
One of you is trying to destroy this ship.
I want duty rosters and activity logs
in my hands in one hour.
Interviews of off-duty personnel
will start immediately.
From now on, we travel in pairs.
-Zaveri and I are armed. Clem is armed.
-[Zaveri] Hey.
We don't know who's the fucking monsters
on this fucking ship.
No one else gets a gun until I'm confident
-you're not trying to destroy my ship.
-[all arguing]
-[Rahim] And I'm here like a fucking sod.
-[Chibuzo] Why do we have guns?
-[Rahim] Fuck off--
-Knock it off!
What, you… you want a reward?
[Malachite] Yeah.
Give me information
that leads to an arrest.
I'll make sure you get an extra share.
-[Shmuel] Yeah. Sure it is.
-[Rahim] That's fucked up,
the whole thing here.
Do you know what I mean?
-[Zaveri] Dismissed.
[Shmuel] He's decided, he is.
-Leave it.
-[sighs]
[Malachite] You're not supposed
to waste food.
-Just leave it, okay?
-[Chibuzo] Can you…
[Rahim] Fucking… With no doctor,
you haven't got fuck all, innit?
I'd love a fucking spotted dick now.
It's quite good.
[whispers] It's running on fumes.
What the fuck does that mean?
-[Malachite] Do you want anything?
-[Shmuel] Just grab a snack and fuck off.
[door opens]
Did you sabotage my ship?
What? No.
-Good. Come with me.
-[sighs]
[Zaveri] I need a way to track this thing.
[Mother] Communication file,
recovery in process.
Estimated progress status:
Twelve percent.
[Rahim] Check the work logs.
I was in the medbay that whole morning.
[Morrow] You're sweating.
[Rahim] Bro.
We've been stuck in a metal tube
for 65 years, breathing recycled farts.
How are you not sweating?
Or is that what it's like
to be a part machine?
You've been calling home. Making plans.
Give up the ship, maybe get rich.
What?
The medbay cameras
have a blind spot. I checked.
-You were off screen for ten minutes.
-[scoffs]
I don't know what to tell you.
Your cameras suck.
And if I check the pharmacy,
am I gonna find anything missing?
That's slander. Slander!
I've been sober…
Enough with the fucking…
A long time. Too long maybe.
Considering… [stammers] …the amount
of bullshit I have to put up with
in this company, you know?
You know.
[stammers]
I just wanna go home, man.
What the…
[grunts]
[grunting]
One sixteenth share.
For what? A little bit of lo mein?
You're taking the piss, mate.
I don't even like lo mein very much.
If I had all the money in the world…
bit of pancake, bit of that hoisin stuff.
You're laughing, mate.
What are you gonna do with your shares
when you get back?
Buy your wife something nice, I bet.
Kid, when I left, my wife was 31.
She looks like my grandmother now.
You see, that's
what they're paying you for.
It's not the work,
it's 65 years of your life.
Equals a quarter of a share.
And then you go, "Oh, yes, please, sir.
Send me on another mission."
[grunts]
I think I ate too much.
Pass me that wrench, will you?
-What?
-The wrench. Pass me the wrench.
-All right. Sorry.
-Come on.
[metallic clicking]
Yeah.
Doesn't creep you out
being down here after…
You better not throw up.
Pass me that goddamn wrench. Come on.
-Jesus, you better not--
-[gags]
I swear to God…
Boss.
Kid.
Kid. Help!
When we took our first readings
from the xenomorph eggs,
we found elevated levels
of gamma radiation.
I should be able to
rig a Geiger counter to…
Oh, my God.
-What?
-Oh, my God.
-Chibuzo.
-She… She's loose.
Who?
The eye.
[alarm blares]
-[metal clattering]
-[Chibuzo gasps]
-We have to go.
-[whimpers]
Right now.
-[Rahim, on intercom] Captain. Zaveri.
-What is it?
I need you in the medbay.
-Can it wait?
-Not if you want him to live.
[sighs]
-We have to seal the door.
-Yeah.
We'll deal with this later.
[Teng] I was on the bridge
when the fuel pod blew.
Check the nav logs.
[Morrow scoffs] Logs can be forged.
Sure.
And some people say
all this is just a simulation.
But that's not the conversation
we're having.
I checked the feed.
You're still visiting her at night,
aren't you?
Doing your filth while she sleeps.
[exhales slowly]
How are you bypassing the keypad?
Or maybe you're using the vents.
Same way you got into
the containment room and set the fire.
You're missing it.
Tell me.
It's right in front of you,
but you can't see it.
What?
Just because the computer says
a cryopod is full doesn't mean it is…
all the time.
There it is.
Someone else is awake.
Who?
[Mother] Estimated progress status:
Ninety-eight percent.
-Recovery complete.
-[machine beeping]
Resolving recovered files.
[tapping buttons]
-[Clem] Hey, Mom. Hey, Dad--
-[taps buttons]
[Bronski] Hey. Um…
I need to tell you something.
I met this woman on the ship,
-and I think I'm in love.
-[taps buttons]
[Malachite] I am a space engineer's
apprentice, so I mean… [laughs] …come on.
I mean, I'm not entirely sure
what apprentice is, but--
[Shmuel] You'd think bureaucracy
only exists on Earth, wouldn't you?
Oh, no, it's up here too.
The red tape that I have to go through
just to fix something.
[taps buttons]
[Petrovitch] I'm tired, bro.
It's too long.
Sixty-five years.
And all the risk that we took.
And the bugs laid eggs in my woman's eyes.
And for what, you know?
A quarter share for a lifetime?
[Boy Kavalier] Yeah, I'm gonna stop you
there because I don't care.
Let me bottom-line this thing.
If the specs you sent are right,
and you can pull this off,
landing the ship in my kingdom,
you're about to be the richest man
in whatever cousin-marrying,
shithole valley you fuck cows in.
[Petrovitch] Yeah, I want a new body.
You can do that now, right, Mr. Kavalier?
Put my mind in a robot
with this, uh, Progeny company you got?
[Boy Kavalier] It's Prodigy. [chuckles]
As in the boy wonder, me.
And yeah. We can do that.
Almost.
You bring me these creatures
and you're gonna go
to the top of the list with a bullet.
[Petrovitch] What if I don't
survive the crash? Hmm?
Well…
Well, that would suck for you,
wouldn't it?
Shit.
[Mother] Containment threat. Medbay One.
Containment threat. Medbay One.
-Where have you been?
-It's Petrovitch, the saboteur.
He's been pretending to be
in cryo but he's loose.
-I should be out looking for him.
-Kid started puking up blood.
Now he won't wake up.
-So it's a security issue or…
-Containment threat. Medbay One.
Containment threat. Medbay One.
-[intercom beeps]
-Talk to me, Doc.
He's losing blood. We don't know why.
We're scanning now.
See these dark spots up
and down his digestive tract?
They're lining the main artery.
[Chibuzo] I'll get the probe.
We can do an upper GI scan.
[Rahim] No time.
[through intercom] I need to open him up.
Stop the bleeding.
-Do it.
-What if it's contamination?
By the time we put him in the cryopod
and freeze him, he'll be dead.
-Do the surgery.
-[Rahim, through intercom] Okay.
[machine whirring]
Fucking hell.
[Rahim] There'll be ground to make.
[screams]
-[Rahim] Fucking hell.
-[Zaveri, through intercom] Talk to me.
Subject has six foreign bodies
lining his esophagus.
[Chibuzo] It's ticks.
They're ticks.
We need to seal that room.
I'm gonna try to remove one.
No!
Nobody asked you.
They're siphoning too much blood.
You wanna lead? Then lead.
Tell him to stop.
Look, back off.
The lady's the captain. It's her call.
Fuck it.
He's only a kid.
[Rahim] Fucking hell.
-[clears throat, grunts]
-[Chibuzo grunts]
[Rahim] Ready?
It's fucked up.
-Dr. Rahim, what are you doing?
-Saving his fucking life.
[Chibuzo whispers] Gently.
Okay.
[both coughing]
[Morrow] No. No.
Seal it. Seal it!
They're dead.
They're all dead.
It got Teng.
-What got him?
-I don't know. Something big.
Okay. Um…
Okay, we need to get to the bridge,
seal ourselves in.
We got enough fuel to get us
into geosynchronous orbit around Earth,
call in a cleaning team.
We just need to figure out
how to shift our trajectory.
Shmuel, go to the engine room,
transfer all function to the bridge.
Clem and I will wake up
the remaining crew.
Go with Shmuel.
Captain.
I'm taking command of the ship.
Move your ass.
[alarm blaring]
Pistol out and up.
-Wait. Which one is Petrovitch again?
-Just focus.
[whispers] Come. It's gonna be all right.
[sighs]
[Clem] What's wrong with Zaveri?
Remember to use the electric rounds.
We can't afford to hurt the specimens.
Hurt them? What about us?
[gun firing]
[Morrow] Oh, fuck.
[shouts]
[Clem] Fuck!
[groaning]
-[gunfire]
-[Clem grunting]
-Come on. Come on.
-[grunting]
Lie down.
Hey, hang in there. Just hang on.
Hang in there.
[shouts, groaning]
-[Morrow shouts]
-[assailant grunting]
Petrovitch, right?
It doesn't matter.
You can't stop it.
Stop what? What did you do?
They want their monsters.
Here they come… [grunts]
[breath trembling]
[grunts]
[screeching]
[alien breathing heavily]
[alarm blaring]
Shmuel.
Where's Morrow?
Shmuel?
We have to seal the door.
Did you hear me? It's coming.
[device buttons buzz]
Zaveri.
Zaveri, get up.
Uh-uh.
[growling, chittering]
Fuck it.
Morrow, let me in!
It's coming.
It's coming!
Fucking asshole!
[Zaveri shouting, grunting]
[humming]
-[♪ "La Mer" playing]
-[humming]
Mother, I need the impact room.
[song continuing]
[song ends]
I'm glad you came in.
No other survivors?
All dead before we hit the ground.
But the cargo survived?
Yes, ma'am.
My grandmother was very fond
of you, you know.
[Morrow] I'm grateful.
She had no reason to take me in.
A feral boy with a palsied arm
begging in the street.
She always said you were
the fiercest thing she had ever seen.
I told her I'd bring the specimens home,
and I will.
And then I'll kill
the one called Kavalier.
He agreed to arbitration.
We meet tomorrow.
Maybe the lawyers can fix this.
Unless lawyers mean soldiers,
we're gonna have to do this my way.
Whatever he wants, he gets.
[drumroll]
[♪ "Cherub Rock" playing]